Hello Hello friends I am Suresh Khandelwal
and welcome to HKG Stock Market
and today we are going to discuss another stock in this
which is ICICI Lombard
General Insurance Company Limited. It is a
general insurance company. Dravid is an insurance company.
It deals in general insurance,
claims management
and investment management.
The company
which had a cross return premium of Rs 43.20
billion, let
us see some information about the company. Now let us see some more information about the company. The
co-founder of the company Bhargav Dasgupta is its
headquarter. ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited is the asset management
or parent organization. And the question is,
ICICI Bank had 12.8 and
its headquarter is in Mumbai and the number
of employers is
1236 and revenue is from 11:00. Surely Surya,
so we have seen some information about the company. Now let
us discuss its
performance today. Its opening today
is
Close also around the same time where Friday
Swift its price was 067 percent and in five days it has
given a negative return of 0.85 percent
and its price had dropped from 10.30 to 10.30 percent. If we
look at one month before, its
price was 15063 percent and in one month it has
again given a negative return of 0.62 percent
and if we look at six months before, its
price was 1650 percent. In six months it has
given a return of only eight percent and in the same period it has given a
return of eight percent. Whereas if we
look at its face performance five years before,
its price was
6105 percent. It has given a very good
return of 128 percent.
Rock Band, if we check its maximum performance, it
is the same and its maximum performance is also
2017 Seth
A Danish said that we would have seen some more information every
day and it is related to this that this
long card block deal launch is angry with one
3.5 70%
101 has
sold its 175 crore shares at 3.57 percent,
so one to one and a half approximate like shares
and 175 crore shares. So from here, if you
see the news, the company which is
175 crore shares is going to
sell its shares through a block deal.
101 was the news due to which its price has
decreased and
in the coming time also, on 12th June, its price can fall further. So, it is
mentioned here that the
block deal of 101 General Insurance
Company was launched on 4th October with the
companies Singh Data's shareholder French
Insurance from 101. The
share will be sold at 3.5 70% office. So,
what is the company going to do with its 3.58 percent tax?
So, due to this news, its
price can also drop further.
If we look at the results of the June quarter, some information has been given here that
long words stand-alone from ICC  Net sales
in June 21 quarter was Rs 10 crore, Rs
6452, 6%. If we look at it on a sequential basis, it has come
down to 64.6 percent. The bank's quarterly
net profit has been Rs 150 crore, which is 1.63 percent
and that too is 61.91 percent.
Last year, the proper net profit in the same June quarter was Rs
398 crore, which has decreased to Rs
151 crore in this quarter, so what has happened is Rs 61.98 crore. The
profit has declined here and the sales have
also decreased by 64.11 percent and if we
compare such serial numbers
with HDFC Life, then
in the last three months, HDFC Life has
given a return of 7.29 percent, whereas, it has
given a return of 2.23 percent, in six months, HDFC Life has given a return of 5 percent,
ICICI Lombard has given a return of 70 percent, if we
look at Ben10, it is 6%.  Life
what is two percent Aslam Ward
21 affair's house If we look at HDFC Life's
98% return and its 121 If we compare it with SBI Life, then
SBI Life has given a
return of twenty four percent in the last three months
It has given a return of negative 2.23 percent
and against this item has given
thirty-seven, then has given 70%
in one year 42% Chief License Number One Else
Dos
Fair has husband 123 percent That market
cap Look at
your cut I had done this tall boy from this The
current price is phase
52-week high is 6 from
Zouk copy value is
61.95 158 The
best Indian rice zero point five two
ROC ho that ad accused's 26.98
21.7 and face value is of tank Whereas if we
look at the profit of the company, then the company
is almost free from the company The company has delivered a good
profit growth
23.75 festival Last five years
Premiers Maintaining good health
Department of  21.33 percent
New Delhi Nagar, if we look at the stop
spreading ads, let's see which one is
stop spreading and 1.7 times
Facebook value promoter holding his
decreases and last quarter, last
quarter planning included income of
493 crores, if we look at its sales
performance, then
in June quarter it was
104 crores, in March it was
more than 300, if we
look at December then it
is 123 in 2010 and
95 in September mobile 2010 and if we look at the profit, then
in September Twenty20, the
phase pieces are allotted to iPad and drop ok f-18, the
day allotted to March is
203 crores, note the profit of 122 crores in June quarter,
but if we
look at the last quarter then it is very high, if we
look at the net profit of which machine from A law, then the net
profit is
1000 for its 6 crores in September and Twenty20  2346 crores and this is the June quarter of
152 crores. Profit is also
gradually decreasing. If
we look at some more information about the company, then the
sales of the company are
growing at 10 percent in the last 10 years
and the profit in the
current year at the level of cent da in it has been
negative
4% in the last year and over the long
period it is growing at 20% from zero. The
Servi stock price has
grown at 6% and the return on equity
is over 80 percent
and in the last twenty years it has grown at 22%.
If we look at its share holding pattern, then
promoters have 51.8 percent,
55 have 29.08, device have 11.96
and public have 7.08.
So for such information,
stay connected to our channel. Thank you.